export const ScienceHard = [
  {
    question: "What is a balanced chemical equation?",
    Options: [
      "The equation in which the number of reactants is equal to the number of products.",
      "The equation in which the size of the reactant is equal to the size of the product.",
      "The equation in which the number of atoms of the reactant is equal to the number of atoms of the product.",
      "The equation in which the number of molecules is equal to the number of products."
    ],
    correct: 3,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Sodium + Water →",
    Options: [
      "Sodium Hydroxide + Hydrogen",
      "Sodium Hydrate + Hydrogen",
      "Sodium Hydroxide + Water",
      "Sodium Hydride + Water"
    ],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "What is the color of the silver chloride?",
    Options: ["Grey", "White", "Brown", "Greenish"],
    correct: 2,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Which thing changes after the rancidity of food?",
    Options: ["Smell and size", "Taste and size", "Smell and taste", "Taste and shape"],
    correct: 3,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "The bases change litmus paper from ___.",
    Options: ["Blue to red", "Red to blue", "Red to orange", "Orange to blue"],
    correct: 2,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following olfactory signals give the information about bases and acids?",
    Options: ["Color", "Odor", "Size", "Shape"],
    correct: 2,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Metal oxide + Acid →",
    Options: ["Salt + Hydrogen", "Metal Hydrate + Hydrogen", "Salt + Water", "Metal Hydrate + Water"],
    correct: 3,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of CaSO4.1/2H2O?",
    Options: ["Baking powder", "Baking soda", "Plaster of Paris", "Gypsum"],
    correct: 3,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following metal is not lustrous?",
    Options: ["Gallium", "Cesium", "Mercury", "Diamond"],
    correct: 4,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Name the metal which is in liquid form at room temperature?",
    Options: ["Mercury", "Gallium", "Cesium", "Diamond"],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Soap creates a structure in the washing process. What is that structure called?",
    Options: ["Micelles", "Tail", "Head", "Hydrophilic"],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "According to Mendeleev's periodic table, what is the basis of the elements' chemical property?",
    Options: ["Charge", "Valency", "Atomic number", "Mass"],
    correct: 4,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "According to Mendeleev's periodic table, which of the following elements belongs to the seventh or first group?",
    Options: ["Helium", "Hydrogen", "Sodium", "Argon"],
    correct: 2,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "What is the number of groups in the modern periodic table?",
    Options: ["18", "17", "10", "12"],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Which group does chlorine belong to?",
    Options: ["Halogen group", "Alkaline metal group", "Alkaline earth metal group", "Noble gas group"],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Name the process by which plants take their nutrition?",
    Options: ["Zylum", "Phloem", "Photosynthesis", "Osmosis"],
    correct: 3,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the gland found in the human mouth?",
    Options: ["Thyroid", "Pitutory", "Gonads", "Salivary"],
    correct: 4,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the main structure in the human body through which gases are exchanged?",
    Options: ["Lungs", "Nose", "Oesophagous", "Alveoli"],
    correct: 4,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "What is the basic unit of the kidney?",
    Options: ["Neuron", "Nephron", "Cell", "Glomerulus"],
    correct: 2,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "What is the basic unit of the nervous system?",
    Options: ["Neuron", "Nephron", "Cell", "Glomerulus"],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  }
];

